eyeos.org 2013-06-06

# eyeOS Privacy Policy - eyeOS

Click to Print This Page  
eyeOS S.L. (“eyeOS” or “We/us”) is committed to protecting the privacy of all the general and registered users (“you” or “user”) of the website at www.eyeos.com (“website”). This Privacy Policy explains our practices regarding the use of personal data collected and processed through our website.  
By using our website and services, and in particular by providing your personal information on registration or contacting us for any reason, you explicitly accept this Privacy Policy and You provide us with full consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal data in accordance with the terms set out in this policy, including the sending of electronic communications.  
We may amend this Privacy Policy as required to adapt it to future legislative or case law developments. We will notify you by posting a clear notice of these changes on our websites and in this Privacy Policy.  
Unless a specific local regulation sets forth to the contrary, the Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of Spain.

### A. Data collection

_**Browsing**_  
We do not collect any personal data if you are merely browsing the website, except as indicated in “Technical data” below. 

_**Web forms**_  
If you submit any webform to us (Contacts, Jobs, Partners, Blog comments, Trial Download), we collect the data indicated in the forms and submitted by you, including name and email address. Required data is indicated. This data is used for processing your request and contacting you for further communication. 

_**Registration**_  
On registering for Demo Services, we will collect the following personal data: name, surname, email address. This data is obligatory and if they are not provided, an account cannot be created. 

**_Prohibited data_**  
In all events, including in the Demo Service, it is forbidden to submit to us or upload to the Services any data that contains sensitive data that is relative to identifiable persons such as: your and or third party’s racial origin, membership in a trade union, religion, ideology and sexual life, your and or third party’s health, unless it proves necessary in order to assert any handicap or disability situation for labour purposes; or your and or third party’s relative to the commission of criminal offences or proceedings and associated penalties or fines; unless such data is encrypted. 

### B. Data use

**_General_**  
The data we collect is used for the development of our professional contact with you and for the management of any newsletters, notification emails or commercial communications in general about the Services and products and any new features, offers or promotions offered by us, provision and management of your Demo Service account and the Services provided to you (as described in the Terms), compliance with the Terms and other legal communications. Registered users are also sent notification emails about activities the Demo Service and Trial version of the Professional Edition. 

**_Disclosure_**  
We treat your personal data with strict confidentiality in accordance with applicable law. However we shall disclose any personally identifiable and/or non personally identifiable information about you or your use of our Services, in compliance with a legal obligation or in order to correctly deliver our Services or perform other obligations in accordance to the applicable regulations and rules set forth in the website Terms. 

**_Use of data by other Users_**  
If you have access to personal data of other Users or persons, you agree to process and use the data in accordance with these terms and only for the explicit purposes of the Services, or otherwise with the consent of the User. You will not submit or publish any personal data relating to any individual that has not been authorized by that person or this Policy. You will protect the confidentiality of any accessible personal data and prevent access by any unauthorized third person. You will inform us within 24 hours about any problem arisen in relation with user data management. You will be responsible for any illegal use by you of other Users’ data, including any use contrary to the applicable data protection laws and/or in violation this Privacy Policy. 

_**Commercial Communications**_  
By filling in and sending your data to us, you expressly consent to receive commercial communications regarding the subject matter of the website and other services in accordance to applicable law, including alerts, notices, newsletters, offers and promotions. If you do not wish to receive information from this Website you can expressly opt out by sending a notification to info@eyeos.com. 

### C. Data Security

We have adopted technical and organizational measures to preserve and protect your personal information from unauthorized use or access and from being altered, lost or misused, taking into account the technological state of art, the features of the information stored and the risks to which information is exposed.  
However, due to the nature of the information and related technology, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of your personal information and expressly disclaims any such obligation. If we learn of a security breach, then we will attempt to notify You electronically so that You can take appropriate steps.

### D. eyeOS as data processor

In registering for a Demo Service account and submitting any third party personal data within the context of this account (“Third Party Data”), you shall be the Data Controller and you appoint us as a Data Processor of such data, for the purpose of providing the Demo Service.  
To the extent that we are such “Data Processor”, we shall (a) implement appropriate technical and organizational measures to safeguard the Third Party Data against any unauthorized or unlawful access, loss, destruction, theft, use or disclosure; (b) limit access to the Third Party Data only to those employees who need to know it to enable the Processor to perform the Services, and shall take appropriate steps to ensure the reliability of those of its employees or subcontractors who have access to such Third Party Data; (c) only process the personal data as specified by this Policy and in accordance with your instructions, and (d) will not use the Third Party Data for any purposes other than those related to the performance of the Services or pursuant to your written instructions. Upon the expiry or termination of this Agreement by way or de-registration, or upon request of the Customer, cease any and all use of the Third Party Data and will destroy or return it to you. We will not disclose the Third Party Data to any third party without your prior written consent of the Customer.  
As Data Processor may provide access to a subcontractor processor to any such Third Party Data if we reasonably consider such access and processing necessary to the performance of the Services. In the event of such access and before the access takes place, we shall ensure that an agreement with the third party is in place which is sufficient to require it to treat personal data in accordance with the applicable provisions of this Agreement and applicable  
We shall provide you with reasonable assistance in the event that you receive a request from an individual or regulator under the data protection laws, provided that you shall first use all reasonable endeavours to resolve the request without our assistance. We shall promptly notify you of any such request received that should properly have been addressed to you.  
You warrant that you have all the appropriate consents from data subjects whose personal data are submitted to us in the course of the provision of the Demo Service. You will indemnify and keep us harmless from all claims, damages and losses we may suffer relating to or arising out of the processing of third party personal data submitted to our systems during the course of the provision of the Services. 

### E. Technical data

**_Cookies._**  
This website uses “cookies”, small data files generated in your computer and associated to users. The cookies used cannot read data from the hard disk. The cookies also enable recognition of the users only when they have been registered so that they do not have to register each time they visit or access areas or services that are reserved exclusively for them. They also provide information on the date and time of the last visit the user made to the website and the content selected in browsing. 

**_Information about your computer._**  
Due to the communications standards on the internet, when you visit the our website we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the site. We also receive the internet protocol (“IP”) address of your computer and the type of web browser you are using. We use this information to analyse overall trends to help improve the service. This information is not shared with third parties without your permission. 

### F. User Rights

You have the right to access, rectify, erase, block and oppose any processing of their personal data. Moreover, you may at any time withdraw your consent to the processing of their personal data and information. This withdrawal will not have retroactive effects but may prevent providing the Services. The above is without prejudice to provisions of Spanish applicable law enabling conservation of data for the purpose of defending our responsibility and complying with mandatory legal obligations. The aforementioned rights may be effective by contacting us at info@eyeos.com or at las Ramblas, 140 4C 08002 Barcelona, Spain. 

### G. User Consent

By completing the Website forms and submitting your personal data, you declare to have read and accepted the terms of this Policy. Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing, you expressly and unequivocally consent to:  
• the collection and processing of your personal data by us in accordance with the indicated purposes and this Policy;  
• the processing of your data outside the European Economic Area by third party data processors (e.g. for the purpose of providing professional services to us such as hosting or database management services); and  
• the receipt of commercial e-mails from us.  
• the communication of the data to other site Users outside the European Economic Area at the request of the User.  
Your consent to personal data collection and processing may be revoked, without retroactive effects, in accordance to Sections 6 and 11 of Spanish Data Protection Law 15/1999.  
Version: 1.0. Date: 14 September 2011.
